<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Deploy Data Science</title>
    <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Deploy Data Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 14:32:36 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Serverless ML Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/serverless-ml-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 14:32:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/serverless-ml-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>Intro Banana ML : A Revolutionary Tool for Cheap and Faster ML Inference
Data science and machine learning are quickly becoming essential tools for businesses across the world. The increasing demand for data-driven solutions and applications has created a need for tools that can help developers build cheaper and faster.
What is Banana ML? Enter Banana ML: a powerful, easy-to-use platform for building modern data science applications faster.
Banana ML is an open source machine learning platform built for developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Web APIs For Data Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/simplifying-data-web-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:22:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/simplifying-data-web-api/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hasura.io is a powerful tool for data science and software engineering that can help you build modern data science applications and APIs faster than ever before. With Hasura&amp;rsquo;s intuitive interface and powerful features, you can develop blazing fast GraphQL and REST APIs with ease.
What is Hasura.io? Hasura.io is a cloud-based platform that makes it easy to develop, deploy and manage secure, modern data science applications and APIs. It provides a unified platform for developing, deploying and managing data-driven applications and APIs in a secure, efficient, and cost-effective manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to PyTorch for Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/intro-to-pytorch-for-deep-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 11:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/intro-to-pytorch-for-deep-learning/</guid>
      <description>PyTorch Pytorch is an open source machine learning framework that accelerates the path from research prototyping to production deployment.
Regression Problem Example Boston Housing Dataset I have used the Boston housing dataset as it is one of the basic and beginner friendly dataset on Kaggle
Python Implementation The implementation creates a simple neural network using pytorch and compares with a baseline linear regression model.
Learnings Some key lessons learnt are to start with simple datasets and compare with baseline model to see the difference of using a non linear type model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Open Source Customer Data Integration Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/data-integration-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 11:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/data-integration-solution/</guid>
      <description>Customer Data Integration The first step even before you can begin to apply data science to a problem consists of loading customer data into your system. Although, trivial when you are doing a one off batch load/read from files or databases. It can quickly become a non-trivial task when data updates often, leading to many data refreshes.
To resolve this problem, data science systems use what are known as data loader/integration platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
