<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deploy Data Science</title>
    <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Deploy Data Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 09:41:51 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.deploydatascience.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Postgres Bulk Data Inserts</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/postgres-bulk-data-inserts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 09:41:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/postgres-bulk-data-inserts/</guid>
      <description>A Definitive Complied Guide for Bulk Inserts to Postgres Taken from a stackoverflow answer as below1 (Note that this answer is about bulk-loading data into an existing DB or to create a new one. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested DB restore performance with pg_restore or psql execution of pg_dump output, much of this doesn&amp;rsquo;t apply since pg_dump and pg_restore already do things like creating triggers and indexes after it finishes a schema+data restore).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serverless ML Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/serverless-ml-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 14:32:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/serverless-ml-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>Intro Banana ML : A Revolutionary Tool for Cheap and Faster ML Inference
Data science and machine learning are quickly becoming essential tools for businesses across the world. The increasing demand for data-driven solutions and applications has created a need for tools that can help developers build cheaper and faster.
What is Banana ML? Enter Banana ML: a powerful, easy-to-use platform for building modern data science applications faster.
Banana ML is an open source machine learning platform built for developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Web APIs For Data Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/simplifying-data-web-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:22:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/simplifying-data-web-api/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hasura.io is a powerful tool for data science and software engineering that can help you build modern data science applications and APIs faster than ever before. With Hasura&amp;rsquo;s intuitive interface and powerful features, you can develop blazing fast GraphQL and REST APIs with ease.
What is Hasura.io? Hasura.io is a cloud-based platform that makes it easy to develop, deploy and manage secure, modern data science applications and APIs. It provides a unified platform for developing, deploying and managing data-driven applications and APIs in a secure, efficient, and cost-effective manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to PyTorch for Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/intro-to-pytorch-for-deep-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 11:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/intro-to-pytorch-for-deep-learning/</guid>
      <description>PyTorch Pytorch is an open source machine learning framework that accelerates the path from research prototyping to production deployment.
Regression Problem Example Boston Housing Dataset I have used the Boston housing dataset as it is one of the basic and beginner friendly dataset on Kaggle
Python Implementation The implementation creates a simple neural network using pytorch and compares with a baseline linear regression model.
Learnings Some key lessons learnt are to start with simple datasets and compare with baseline model to see the difference of using a non linear type model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Open Source Customer Data Integration Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/data-integration-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 11:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/posts/data-integration-solution/</guid>
      <description>Customer Data Integration The first step even before you can begin to apply data science to a problem, consists of loading customer data into your system. Although, trivial when you are doing a one off batch load/read from files or databases. It can quickly become a non-trivial task when data updates often, leading to many data refreshes.
To resolve this problem, data science systems use what are known as data loader/integration platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there, Welcome! to Deploy Data Science, a blog for all things data science and ML ops.
Created by Harshal, for ML and data science enthusiasts who would like to go beyond the prototype solutions and learn how to deploy data science from scratch into an end-to-end solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/resources/</guid>
      <description>Awesome List of Data Science Resources Data Engineering
Playlist of Awesome Data Engineering Videos Machine Learning
API Flask
https://github.com/exleym/Flask-Filter Filtering library directly on top of flask Similar libs: https://github.com/juliotrigo/sqlalchemy-filters https://github.com/gorilla-co/odata-query https://github.com/rochacbruno/dynaconf/ Configuration management for Flask in Production environments DevOps Nginx
https://github.com/digitalocean/nginxconfig.io NGINX config generator on steroids. Documentation
docusaurus https://docusaurus.io/ APIs
Hasura - Hasura gives you instant GraphQL &amp;amp; REST APIs on new &amp;amp; existing data sources. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>https://www.deploydatascience.com/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.deploydatascience.com/tags/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
